大家好，欢迎收听今日科技播客。今天是2025-05-26，我为大家带来143条最新科技资讯。
首先，让我们来看看今天的重点新闻。
第1条新闻：Thats Not My Burnout。
据A List Apart报道，Are you like me, reading about people fading away as they burn
out, and feeling unable to relate。
Do you feel like your feelings are invisible to the.
第2条新闻：Asynchronous Design Critique: Giving Feedback。
据A List Apart报道，Feedback, in whichever form it takes, and whatever it may be
called, is one of the most effective soft skills that we have at our disposal to
collabor。
第3条新闻：Asynchronous Design Critique: Getting Feedback。
据A List Apart报道，Any comment。
is probably one of the worst ways to ask for feedback.
Its vague and open ended, and it doesnt provide any indication of what were
lookin.
第4条新闻：Designing for the Unexpected。
据A List Apart报道，Im not sure when I first heard this quote, but its something
that has stayed with me over the years。
How do you create services for situations you can.
第5条新闻：Voice Content and Usability。
据A List Apart报道，Weve been having conversations for thousands of years。
Whether to convey information, conduct transactions, or simply to check in on
one another, peop.
接下来是今日科技快讯。
快讯1：Sustainable Web Design, An Excerpt。
快讯2：Design for Safety, An Excerpt。
快讯3：A Content Model Is Not a Design System。
以上就是今天的科技资讯播报。感谢大家的收听，我们明天同一时间再见。